Before going there
Before
I do want
going
there
I
do
want
to that we
to
think after
that
we
think
after
this short term
this
period of discomfort
short
term
period
of
discomfort
and it is
and
uncomfortable believe me
it
is
uncomfortable
believe
me
I know
I
that the
know
that
the
rolling recession we've
rolling
seen in the
recession
we've
seen
in
the
last few years
last
will turn
few
years
will
turn
into a recovery
into
and we're
a
recovery
and
we're
getting some green
getting
shoots already Employment
some
green
shoots
already
Employment
lags so the
lags
unemployment rate probably
so
the
unemployment
rate
probably
will continue
will
moving up
continue
moving
up
even as this
even
recovery gets underway
as
this
recovery
gets
underway
And then we
And
think next year
then
we
think
next
year
we will be
we
in much more
will
be
in
much
more
of a
of
productivity driven
a
productivity
driven
almost boom in
almost
economic activity mostly
boom
in
economic
activity
mostly
because of
because
this chart
of
this
chart
And I know
And
I've presented it
I
know
I've
presented
it
for those of
for
you who haven't
those
of
you
who
haven't
seen it I
seen
wanted to make
it
I
wanted
to
make
sure everybody has
sure
everybody
has
seen this everyone
seen
interested in
this
everyone
interested
in
the know
the
know